# RESUME

# JUMANA HASEEN

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

ONLINE-PORTFOLIO WEBSITE

HTTPS://JUMANA07.GITHUB.IO/JUMANAHASEENPORTFOLIO-PROJECT/





+91-9940766819



jumanahaseen07@gmail.com



Urapakkam, Chengal pattu



jumanahaseen07@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/juman a-haseen-3608718b/

# SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Javascript
- · React.Js
- Github
- Figma
- Jsx

# EDUCATION

#### HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL

Seventh Day Adventist 2011-2012 67.5%

### SECONDARY SCHOOL

Private

2009-2010 73.6%

#### **BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING**

Computer science & engineering
M.A.M COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING
2012-2016 7.08 (CGPA)

# PROFILE SUMMARY

I have a 4 year and 6 months career break on full time parenting and currently looking for job roles to relaunch my career as fresher ,open to fresh front end developer job profiles and will contribute my 100% to the growth of the company with my acquired skills and ready to quickly learn and execute new skills, Currently Pursuing **FRONT-END** 

**DEVELOPER COURSE from META on COURSERA** 

# EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER (SELF-PRACTICE) Sep 2022-At Present

# Frontend web developer course from Meta (Online)

 Create small projects regarding front-end web development to excel my skill set and dedicating my time towards upskilling myself

FULL-TIME-PARENTING 2018-Aug 2022

DATA CONVERSION SPECIALIST

Feb 2017-June 2017

#### **HTC GLOBAL**

· Worked as a DCS in a Newspaper Project in Excel

# PROJECTS& CERTIFICATION

#### **RESUME PORTAL WEBSITE**

https://jumana07.github.io/My-Simple-Portfolio-Project/

# HAIR-SPA PROMO PAGE

https://jumana07.github.io/Hair-DayPromo/

MY-SMALL QUIZ APP

https://jumana07.github.io/MySmallQuizApp/

## PRICE-ENQUIRY CHATBOT-APP

https://jumana07.github.io/PriceEnquiry-Chatbot/

#### **FLIP-CARD PROJECT**

https://jumana07.github.io/Flip-card-Project/